[ Watch on KissFlix.co ]
DEFAMATION LAWSUIT
Being sued by such a bigshot politician…
It's a special skill.
It’s no laughing matter.
A claim for 300 million in damages!
Guess he's finally out of luck, huh?
Knowing that lawyer, he must have some kind of plan.
I’m not so sure about this time.
Well, let’s see which way the wind blows.
The defendant asserted that the plaintiff, Representative Furuse Yoshichika,
received slush funds, conducted political maneuvering,
and was suspected of involvement in a murder case.
They stated as such to RGC Resorts Representative Kang.
Do you possess objective evidence to support that assertion?
Defense Counsel?
We are looking into it.
In other words, when you made the assertion to Representative Kang,
you did not even have evidence.
We are investigating that too.
For now, there's no evidence?
Go ahead.
This is the file the defendant presented to Representative Kang.
It contains serious accusations, claiming money was used as slush funds
and that Furuse ordered articles fabricated
for use in political strategies.
Yet, according to the defendant,
there is not a single piece of evidence.
Furthermore, this magazine was never even published.
Defense Counsel,
can you present objective evidence to support your claims?
We're looking into it.
Defense Counsel,
please review and secure evidence before the next session.
NO EVIDENCE
ORDERED A TABLOID TO FABRICATE ARTICLES?
If we don't have some kind of evidence, we’re going to lose!
-Evidence of wrongdoing? -Yes!
Anything connecting Furuse and Sendo.
You say that, but Sendo is taking all the blame.
The money trail might not lead back to Furuse.
What about witnesses or a whistleblower?
Trying to find someone now is going to be tough.
It doesn't matter.
I don't care whether we win or lose the trial.
No, we're talking about 300 million here!
The 300 million is just a threat.
If they sue for obstruction of business and defamation,
it will be ten million at most.
Even ten million is a bit tough for us, though.
This trial has only one purpose.
To drag them into court.
We received a report from Mr. Shoji.
The Uramawashi side has no means of proving anything.
Hmm? Of course.
We’re not doing anything illegal, after all.
Looks like a guaranteed win.
More importantly,
we caused quite a bit of trouble for Representative Kang, didn't we?
I will apologize to him once more.
All that’s left is the trial.
Win or lose,
they can't keep interfering with our resort project.
That said,
the wind is blowing in our favor.
I heard from Mr. Kureta.
He said you covered for them.
Could it be you are starting to have doubts about Mr. Furuse?
That was
just a passing whim.
Mr. Furuse is like a father to me.
Besides,
I cannot trust that Uramawashi man.
Donghyuk,
don't you want to know the truth?
When you hide something or lie to yourself,
tragedy is always born from lies.
I simply want to bring the truth to light.
Hey.
What?
-Can he really be trusted? -Who knows…
But, last time…
Annyeonghaseyo.
Hello.
Yo.
You finally came to see me, huh?
I still don't trust you.
I only came to help Yukari bring the truth to light.
A formidable rival, I see.
So, what is it that you want to know?
You used Yukari to get me to come here.
There must be something you want to know, right?
Exactly.
Capable men always get straight to the point. I like that.
Transcripts?
Yes.
Transcripts of the meetings between the RGC side and Japan's resort project team.
Everything from recent years--
Wait a minute.
If he gives us the transcripts, he will--
We won't submit them as evidence.
We’ll merely use them for reference.
-But-- -I…
"I played by the rules and gave it my all. I have no regrets."
When you fail to save Miyuki, can you say that?
I don't mind.
I will show you the transcripts.
I also only wish for one thing.
I want to know the truth.
RESORT PROJECT TRANSCRIPTS
They are all uploaded here.
Regular meetings, company selection meetings,
financial reporting meetings, meetings this, meetings that…
It’s a national project, it's only natural to have so many…
Excuse me.
How many pages is this for just one meeting?
-Are we going to read all of this? -First, go back five years.
Write down every single company name that appears in the transcripts.
-Five years? -All of them?
All right, let's do this!
Compared to the bar exam, this is nothing!
Here you go.
Let's do our best. Right? Ms. Aso. Let's work together.
COPYING DATA
Mitsukura & Co…
Habu!
Wouldn't it be easier to use AI for this? Look.
Nakazaki, you're so smart sometimes!
Here, the name is cut off midway.
This translation app is no good. It's strangely off.
You're right, it abbreviated a lot.
Nichio Construction.
-Kagura Urban Development. -Toto Electric.
Yasui Securities.
T&U Agency. Mitsukura & Co.
I already added Mitsukura & Co.
Bring the companies that came up more than once over here.
Keiyo Travel--
I bought some food!
Nakazaki, you're amazing! It's all about the salmon!
-Right? -You're drinking again.
At this hour, drinking makes me work faster.
Is that really true?
Okay. Let's work even harder!
-Do we have tuna or kombu? -No.
What a big network!
As expected, it’s all big corporations.
Well, it’s a national project.
Done! Five years' worth.
CONSTRUCTION / ENERGY
-Wait! -Hey!
-Hold on a second! -Why are you doing that?
We put in so much effort!
Oh no, wait a minute!
-The fruits of our all-nighter! -Why?
The companies left here…
Investigate them again, in detail.
Huh?
But aren't these all companies we've never heard of before?
That’s precisely why.
They are companies that normally shouldn't be involved
in a national project.
Why are they here? Here!
You mean, they may be pawns for someone in power.
Correct. You've gotten better at this.
I see.
All right, let's look into these companies.
President, board members, business details, everything.
-Yes. -Okay.
The Uramawashi side has not submitted any new briefs or evidence.
If they cannot submit anything by the next hearing,
the court will decide that there is no need to continue any further
and will close the case.
They say a cornered rat will bite the cat.
T&U Agency?
Yes.
A small advertising agency with only 15 employees.
Normally, a company this small wouldn't be in a national project, right?
They are developing the payment system to be used in the resort.
Payment system?
An ad agency?
I remember this company.
Really?
Yes.
RGC said this company had no track record,
so it would be difficult to let them work on the project,
but the Japanese insisted.
The Japanese…
So a politician?
Yes.
I remember Mr. Furuse intervening in its favor.
It's really fishy, isn't it?
There’s one more thing.
Among the board members, there is an interesting man.
As before, the defendant has submitted no objective evidence proving
the plaintiff's wrongdoing.
-Therefore-- -Your Honor.
I'm submitting
new evidence.
T&U Agency, an advertising agency with 15 employees.
The director, Kazuhiko Kiriyama,
is the son of Kotaro Kiriyama, head of Mr. Furuse's supporters' association.
He produced election posters for Mr. Furuse for years,
as well as his newsletter and website--
This is a defamation lawsuit.
Who produces the election posters is not relevant.
The defendant’s conclusion--
What was this company tasked to do in this resort project?
System development.
Worth 2.7 billion yen.
This system is already undergoing trial operation
and is scheduled to be introduced at the next Expo.
They seem to be quite trusted.
However, T&U Agency has no track record in system development.
The actual development has been outsourced.
And this payment system has a catch.
A PROFIT-GENERATING LOOP
At the resort, certain products and services will have reduced tax.
The reduced amount is added to the payment system's transaction fees.
In other words,
a company with no track record,
which has supported Mr. Furuse's political activities for many years,
now has exclusive access
to a business that continues to generate vast profits.
Your Honor!
This evidence doesn't prove the plaintiff profits from this!
-This is unfair! -Well then…
Let's ask him in person.
The defense calls for an examination of the plaintiff,
Mr. Furuse Yoshichika.
The tide of the trial has changed.
I think even Furuse's side is flustered.
If we break them down here,
I think there will also be progress in Mr. Takeshi Nitou's case.
Is that what my brother said?
Not in those exact words,
but I'm sure he has something in mind.
Please be very careful.
Back then, they produced evidence and testimony out of nowhere,
and in an instant, the tide turned.
It’s all right.
I promise I will win this trial, and the retrial too.
Let's hang in there together.
For Taiji's sake too.
Yeah.
Moving on to the next news.
The lawsuit between Mr. Furuse and Attorney Naotoshi Uramawashi
has had a new development.
The defense side has applied to examine Mr. Furuse himself.
-The plaintiff side… -Mr. Furuse…
I wonder if he'll come.
I don't know.
But it’s our chance.
Donghyuk, I have one more request.
Could you testify as a witness for the defense side?
That is--
I know.
If you take the witness stand,
you will be in complete opposition to Mr. Furuse.
But, I want to resolve the case here.
Very well.
Thank you very much.
I also have something I want to speak to you about.
What?
Thank you.
This is the last piece.
Only after doubting everything does the truth become visible.
What is the meaning of this?
I am terribly sorry.
-I didn't think they could-- -Enough with the excuses.
Please tell me what we are going to do from here.
You came here because you have a plan, right?
No, about that…
Murota,
what do you think?
Excuse me.
We were waiting for you.
FOURTH HEARING
We understand Mr. Furuse is to be examined today,
but it seems he has official duties today and won't be able to attend.
We will move Mr. Furuse's examination to a later time.
Now, let's proceed with the witness examination,
originally scheduled after that.
Witness for the defense, Lee Donghyuk.
DEFENSE WITNESS EXAMINATION
Having T&U Agency participate in the resort project
was Mr. Furuse's call, right?
That is incorrect.
Mr. Furuse was not involved at all.
Please wait.
As the negotiator for the RGC side,
you had many discussions with Mr. Furuse, correct?
I only had discussions with Mr. Murota.
Were you ever requested by Mr. Furuse to use T&U?
No.
The one who gave the instructions was Mr. Furuse, right?
It was Mr. Murota.
Really?
Yes.
Defense Counsel, will that be all?
We will now conclude the witness examination
of Mr. Lee Donghyuk.
Next, witness for the plaintiff, Takashi Murota.
PLAINTIFF WITNESS EXAMINATION
Witness,
regarding T&U Agency's participation in the resort project,
did you ever receive instructions from Mr. Furuse?
No.
Then,
who made the decision?
It was me.
T&U's participation
and the contract for the payment system were all my decisions.
It’s a 2.7 billion yen contract!
A secretary can't do it without Mr. Furuse's--
Mr. Furuse does not know.
He was never involved in this matter.
All responsibility lies with me.
A scapegoat.
I see.
ACTED BEHIND HIS BACK?
Good work.
I’m glad to have been of service.
The opponent must not have expected it.
With this, the hand of the law can't touch you now.
Murota, I'm sorry, for making you take the fall.
Yes.
It will be all right, won't it, Mr. Shoji?
Oh, yes.
If they cannot prove that Mr. Murota received money,
he will not be indicted.
Please rest assured.
Will it really be all right?
What’s wrong?
If you want to be my successor, you can't show weakness.
Keep your mind strong.
Yes.
It will be fine.
I always tie up loose ends.
No matter what happens, I will take care of you and your family,
-Don't worry. -Yes.
-Yes? -Mr. Takashi Murota?
I'm Matoba from the MPD.
May we discuss the resort project?
Sure.
Where are we?
The media is camped out front. We’ll enter through the back.
Mr. Furuse already spoke to you, right? Let's settle this quietly…
About the payment system,
was it really a decision you made on your own?
Yes.
I caused Mr. Furuse worry and trouble in a matter he had no knowledge of.
I see.
The reason we had you come here today is actually for a different matter.
The murder of Takeshi Nitou, by Miyuki Shiramoto.
There has been new information.
Actually, a certain item was found.
What?
Yes?
Mr. Furuse.
What is it?
We have a problem.
Donghyuk?
It was like this, wasn't it?
Back then, this was a multi-story parking lot.
No one remembers anymore, though.
And, the incident that happened…
There are hardly any people left who remember it.
What are you talking about?
Murota?
Those are real investigators.
He would never doubt them.
We found Takeshi Nitou's suicide note.
Just a short while ago, Mr. Furuse submitted it.
He did?
He said he found it in your desk.
What?
The one who set it all up was you, wasn't it?
He's setting me up for this too…
This is a childish trick.
I didn't want to do it! But he…
What's wrong?
What about him?
Tell us everything.
Do you understand now?
Furuse is not going to protect you.
I didn't have a choice!
You're playing dirty.
You too.
You guys are the same, right?
Well, no matter what he says, it has nothing to do with me.
You're being quite cold.
He's your successor, isn't he?
Successor?
This line of work isn't for the faint of heart.
Besides, I can easily find a replacement secretary.
Did you hear that?
We never said the video was live.
You were completely fooled.
Hurry!
Oh no!
You understand now, don't you?
Furuse does not plan to protect you.
I'm a busy man, so if you'll excuse me.
No turning back now. Why not see it through?
The players are all here.
You have the best seat.
Now, can you tell us the truth?
During land development--
Murota.
During the land development, people complained of a foul odor.
We oppose the redevelopment!
The opposition was fierce, so we tested the water immediately.
Just before the results came out, Mr. Furuse called me in.
Mr. Nitou is an upright man.
I'm counting on you.
Very well.
Back then, I was his second secretary.
He told me to fake the data.
LOWEST VALUES
However, Ms. Shiramoto doubted the test results,
investigated independently,
and found out that the numbers didn't add up.
Receiving that report, Mr. Nitou realized the falsification…
Do you understand what you've done?
But these documents are submitted under your name. It's already too late--
You bastard!
What's wrong? You're being so loud.
Oh, no…
Mr. Nitou,
I highly value your honesty.
However, politics isn't so straightforward.
I would like you to be a bit more understanding.
But this is falsification.
Only if someone finds out.
Listen carefully.
If this problem comes to light,
the one held accountable will be you, Mr. Nitou.
Of course, it could also become a problem for me and the entire party.
That's not all.
The tens of thousands of people involved in this plan,
and the lives of their families,
will be greatly affected.
Are you prepared to sacrifice all that just to stick to your honesty?
Do you have that resolve?
Do you, Mr. Nitou?
My apologies.
However…
You don't need to worry.
I always tie up loose ends.
No matter what happens,
I will take good care of you
and your family, Mr. Nitou.
Got it?
Mr. Furuse asked me to keep an eye on Mr. Nitou.
And…
I lost sight of him for a brief moment…
I tried to call out to him, but it happened in a split second.
What?
Mr. Nitou!
Suicide?
Mr. Furuse hated being investigated.
It was then that…
Oh, please wait a moment.
MIYUKI SHIRAMOTO ABOUT THE WATER POLLUTION
Sir.
I have an idea.
Yes.
I used Mr. Nitou's phone to send a message to Ms. Shiramoto and called her over.
Mr. Nitou.
Mr. Nitou!
Mr. Nitou, can you hear me?
After that, you pulled the strings.
Right?
JUSTICE'S FORM WAS A SHAM
SHE'S A HYPOCRITE MURDERER!
A righteous lawyer was actually involved in shady deals
and eventually committed murder.
That was the story.
The public took the bait.
IT'S UNTHINKABLE THAT A DEFENDER OF THE PEOPLE WOULD DO THIS
No, not just the public!
At that time,
even though there was a discrepancy in Mr. Nitou's estimated time of death,
no one inside the police force pointed it out.
Thus, Ms. Shiramoto was framed for a crime she didn't commit.
I always…
I always found it strange.
I also have something I want to speak to you about.
What?
I received a message from my father.
The day before he died.
From your father?
Yes.
BE STRONG. I'M PROUD OF YOU.
Back then, we were living far apart,
so I thought he only sent it to cheer me on.
-But thinking about it now-- -This was…
A will.
There was no way they could find the true culprit.
Because it was suicide, after all.
In order to find out the truth,
we needed you and Murota to fight us in court.
That's why… I provoked you into filing the lawsuit.
Donghyuk intentionally let you know he would stand as a witness for the defense.
Seeing that things were going sour, you used this chance to cut Murota loose.
From the moment we framed Tajima and returned Murota to your side,
this operation had already begun.
-Murota. -Yes.
I'll need you to come back here soon.
I understand.
You thought you had us in the palm of your hand,
but you were the one being played.
So what?
You are lawyers, aren't you?
You should proceed based on facts, not wild assertions.
Do you have any evidence for what you just said?
Well?
We found a suicide note.
You really never learn, do you? That nonsense again…
How do you know it's nonsense?
Sir, I'm sorry.
"I'm sorry" isn't going to cut it.
Back then, you never mentioned this.
Is this another one of your lies?
Well? Is it?
"Back then"…
When are you referring to?
This is the record of the data falsification that Mr. Murota carried out.
In any case,
it has nothing to do with me.
You don't get it, do you?
Because you ran your mouth,
Murota's testimony turned into certainty.
On top of that, if we have the falsified data,
we can prove without a doubt Mr. Takeshi Nitou's suicide as well.
Ridiculous.
Not a bad story, Mr. Uramawashi.
As fiction, that is.
It's non-fiction, though.
Wait!
Our conversation isn't over yet.
Donghyuk.
-Do we let him go? -Leave him be.
Our goal is to clear Miyuki's name.
We have all the evidence now.
What you said just now, we will have you repeat it to the police.
We have the video, so there's no use keeping quiet.
What you did can get you charged with abandonment of a corpse.
Mr. Matoba is waiting at the police station.
He said, "Let's put an end to the past."
It's game over.
The murder case of Secretary Nitou, which happened ten years ago,
has new developments.
Former lawyer Miyuki Shiramoto, currently serving a sentence,
is having her retrial request processed,
as there is a possibility she was falsely accused.
Furthermore, internal documents
have surfaced suggesting that after the incident,
Furuse's team abused information
and lobbied the media in an attempt to direct public opinion.
There are increasing demands for the truth to be revealed.
Mr. Furuse!
They are suspecting you manipulated public opinion ten years ago.
This is an extremely regrettable situation.
T&U Agency's payment system has been frozen, and there are concerns
this might affect the resort project.
May I say a few words?
For every large project, like this one,
people always bring up past failures.
Donghyuk.
Politics, you see…
It's a war.
Sacrifices are an inevitable part of it.
Please understand that.
This resort project is also your father's long-cherished wish.
That is precisely why,
no matter what happens, I will not give up.
Mr. Furuse completely denied the allegations
of public opinion manipulation over his secretary's murder.
He also emphasized the necessity of the resort project to the public,
and left the party headquarters…
Ms. Shiramoto,
your request for a retrial has been completed.
The legal revision has passed too, and I hope we get the results soon.
Thank you.
We already know you're innocent. Why can't they just let you out?
No.
It was my fault for not fighting back.
Besides, I think a verdict that has been finalized
shouldn't be easily overturned.
That's why laws are drawn up, and why we lawyers exist.
Yukari.
Once again,
thank you so much.
Ms. Shiramoto…
You fought for me,
risking your own life.
I can't thank you enough.
It's thanks to you.
Your principles made me who I am today.
Are you really going to quit?
I was never fit to be a lawyer anyway.
I agree with you on that,
but from here on in will be the hardest part.
A retrial request takes a dizzyingly long time to be granted.
I think we already have a better person for the job.
-I couldn't say this all this time, but… -Yeah?
I apologize for the trouble I caused you.
What's this?
Is it going to snow or something?
Once Miyuki is free, the three of us…
No,
the four of us should go for a drink.
I think hell just froze over.
Who knew the handwritten note in the article was significant?
We have this proof in writing,
so even if the testimony changes, this part can be evidence.
Mr. Uramawashi saw that far ahead?
It sends chills down my spine.
Nothing got past him!
Online opinion has changed too.
That's because the major media are reporting it on a large scale.
Now even the public is all "She was innocent!"
Public opinion is always so fickle.
I'm going home.
Goodbye.
-Bye. -Bye.
Excuse me.
Will she stop coming here now?
Won't you be sad?
Hey, I don't really--
Now's the time to tell her how you feel.
Do you think I have a chance?
-Yeah. -No way in hell.
-It's fine… -Do it now!
Are you really quitting?
Ms. Shiramoto's innocence hasn't been recognized yet, you know.
I feel kind of tired.
What?
I'll leave the rest to you.
"Leave it to me," you say…
Don't push the most exhausting part onto me!
I thought you hated being dragged around by me?
From now on, you can fight fair and square,
your own way.
Do you think you get to say that?
Because of you, my convictions are in shreds.
It's fine.
A foolishly honest person like you can't become like me.
Are you complimenting me, or insulting me?
I'm complimenting you.
That's a lie, isn't it?
Thank you for everything.
I'm grateful.
I bet that's also a lie.
Well then…
Goodbye.
I'm sure that was…
also a lie, right?
Mr. Fujiwara!
My wife and I rarely agreed…
I got scammed at a beauty salon.
You get a good deal if you start today!
There must be an opening somewhere!
-You said it was the last time! -Make me your apprentice!
You're not fit to be a lawyer.
You've become a better lawyer than before.
That was a lie.
What?!
Subtitle translation by: Nix S.